Similar to this tool, we have another tool that was also commonly abused by other
detectors too.
In many incidents, I have handled the tool name of netscan.exe.
This is one of a nice tool to enumerate the network-based information from the organization.
You can get netscan from Google, it's kind of, it needs to search for netscan.
IP scanner download.
So you can see there is a soft perfect network scanner.
You can download it and install it in your machine.
So once you install the software, it will be looked like this.
And you need to use the IP address here and you need to give the path here and you
can run starts scanning.
So instead of running in the command line interface, this is pretty easy one.
So the term is not recognized.
It may be, first changed in another directory, let people change the directory here.
It is, let's copy this sub path and move towards the command.
The path was like, different, let's, and remove the double quotes.
Let's execute and now it was saying the target already.
So once, once the scan was done, you can find the result and documents on the scan
has been completed, but it will take some time for scanning.
Something will be like, the results will be like, similar.
It will only show which of the host, host are online and offline, what are the information
that's all.
Yeah.
So as per your thing, you can use any kind of tools if you need advanced IP scanner,
IP scanner, let's scan.
We have some other scanners also.
So based on your tactics, you can go ahead with a different different scanners.
Okay.
So that's all about this video.
I hope we completed a few of the discovery tools and we'll jump on to the next one.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Bye.